import type { VocabularyQuizQuestion } from "~/types/quiz/vocabulary-quiz";


export const mockWordQuizQuestions : VocabularyQuizQuestion[] = 
[ 
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'house'?",
      translation: "ev",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "ev",
      option2: "araba",
      option3: "kitap",
      option4: "su",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
  },
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'water'?",
      translation: "su",
      correctAnswer: 4,
      option1: "ev",
      option2: "araba",
      option3: "kitap",
      option4: "su",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'book'?",
      translation: "kitap",
      correctAnswer: 3,
      option1: "ev",
      option2: "araba",
      option3: "kitap",
      option4: "su",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'car'?",
      translation: "araba",
      correctAnswer: 2,
      option1: "ev",
      option2: "araba",
      option3: "kitap",
      option4: "su",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'tree'?",
      translation: "ağaç",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "ağaç",
      option2: "çiçek",
      option3: "güneş",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'flower'?",
      translation: "çiçek",
      correctAnswer: 2,
      option1: "ağaç",
      option2: "çiçek",
      option3: "güneş",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'sun'?",
      translation: "güneş",
      correctAnswer: 3,
      option1: "ağaç",
      option2: "çiçek",
      option3: "güneş",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'moon'?",
      translation: "ay",
      correctAnswer: 4,
      option1: "ağaç",
      option2: "çiçek",
      option3: "güneş",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'friend'?",
      translation: "arkadaş",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "arkadaş",
      option2: "aile",
      option3: "anne",
      option4: "baba",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'family'?",
      translation: "aile",
      correctAnswer: 2,
      option1: "arkadaş",
      option2: "aile",
      option3: "anne",
      option4: "baba",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'mother'?",
      translation: "anne",
      correctAnswer: 3,
      option1: "arkadaş",
      option2: "aile",
      option3: "anne",
      option4: "baba",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'father'?",
      translation: "baba",
      correctAnswer: 4,
      option1: "arkadaş",
      option2: "aile",
      option3: "anne",
      option4: "baba",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'food'?",
      translation: "yemek",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "yemek",
      option2: "içecek",
      option3: "ekmek",
      option4: "et",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'drink'?",
      translation: "içecek",
      correctAnswer: 2,
      option1: "yemek",
      option2: "içecek",
      option3: "ekmek",
      option4: "et",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'bread'?",
      translation: "ekmek",
      correctAnswer: 3,
      option1: "yemek",
      option2: "içecek",
      option3: "ekmek",
      option4: "et",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'meat'?",
      translation: "et",
      correctAnswer: 4,
      option1: "yemek",
      option2: "içecek",
      option3: "ekmek",
      option4: "et",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
  {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'time'?",
      translation: "zaman",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "zaman",
      option2: "gün",
      option3: "hafta",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'day'?",
      translation: "gün",
      correctAnswer: 2,
      option1: "zaman",
      option2: "gün",
      option3: "hafta",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'week'?",
      translation: "hafta",
      correctAnswer: 3,
      option1: "zaman",
      option2: "gün",
      option3: "hafta",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "What is the Turkish word for 'month'?",
      translation: "ay",
      correctAnswer: 4,
      option1: "zaman",
      option2: "gün",
      option3: "hafta",
      option4: "ay",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    }
]


export const mockExpressionQuizQuestions : VocabularyQuizQuestion[] = 
[
  {
      question: "How do you say 'Hello' in Turkish?",
      translation: "Merhaba",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "Merhaba",
      option2: "Güle güle",
      option3: "Teşekkür ederim",
      option4: "Özür dilerim",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "How do you say 'Goodbye' in Turkish?",
      translation: "Güle güle",
      correctAnswer: 2,
      option1: "Merhaba",
      option2: "Güle güle",
      option3: "Teşekkür ederim",
      option4: "Özür dilerim",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "How do you say 'Thank you' in Turkish?",
      translation: "Teşekkür ederim",
      correctAnswer: 3,
      option1: "Merhaba",
      option2: "Güle güle",
      option3: "Teşekkür ederim",
      option4: "Özür dilerim",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
  {
      question: "How do you say 'Sorry' in Turkish?",
      translation: "Özür dilerim",
      correctAnswer: 4,
      option1: "Merhaba",
      option2: "Güle güle",
      option3: "Teşekkür ederim",
      option4: "Özür dilerim",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    },
   {
      question: "How do you say 'How are you?' in Turkish?",
      translation: "Nasılsın?",
      correctAnswer: 1,
      option1: "Nasılsın?",
      option2: "Ne yapıyorsun?",
      option3: "Nerede yaşıyorsun?",
      option4: "Kaç yaşındasın?",
      note: null,
      type: 1,
      id: 1,
      difficulty: 1,
    }
]